doesn't go well, because
it's not always going to go well.
And it shouldn't.
These (Asian) women are not there.
No.
Not every single match.
And it shouldn't be.
These (Thai) women are not there to all like you.
(International) Dating is a little bit like making
sausage. You really don't want to, you
know, look at the process, but the
end product is usually pretty good.
And I will say that, you know, with
the dating, there's good, bad, and ugly.
And, you know, there's going to be
some wonderful things that happen,
and there's going to be some
things that are not so wonderful.
And, Tom, you and I were talking earlier.
I go with eyes wide open.
Yeah.
The bad, everything,
it's going to happen.
Here's the key, I think for most
people, they take it too personal.
And it's not personal,
it's about finding a (genuine) match.
Right.
And when you find a match, it works.
Yeah.
And one of the things
that, and you should touch
on this, because I
think it's really important.
A lot of what happens on
these (dating) tours is between the ears.
Yeah.
It's your mindset.
It's how you deal with
things that are coming at you.
Because there's going to be a lot of
things coming at you on a tour, right?
All these (Bangkok) women, the
interpreters, the staff, the
foreign country, the foreign
food, the foreign language.
All this is coming at you.
How do you deal with it?
Do you get overwhelmed?
Do you get too nervous?
Do you shut down?
Or do you just try to relax and listen
to what we're saying and deal with it?
And if something does
not go right, don't pull
into a shell, but just say,
okay, you know what?
There's another day.
There's another opportunity.
And if you look at it
that way, you'll do well.
But (Foreigners) some guys, if they go out
on a date and it doesn't go well,
maybe it was a (Asian)woman that
they were really looking forward to,
and it just doesn't go well, because
it's not always going to go well.
And it shouldn't.
These (Thai) women are not there.
No.
Not every single match.
And it shouldn't be.
These women are not there to all like you.
Like, they're not being paid to like you.
It's not like, what was that Westworld
where they were all machines?
Remember that movie?
And they were robots, and
they went in, and they, yeah.
It's not like that.
These are real (Asian) women
with real lives, with real
problems, with real things
going on in their lives.
They're not in a box
waiting for us to come over.
Some guys, I think, really think,
well, I'm coming, so they get, no.
They have stuff going on, as
you know, because you're waiting.
I'll tell you, in all
the tours I've ever
been to, the group
tours, there's always one.
That just can't get out of his own way.
And he's not having fun, and
he's miserable, and he's grumpy.
And I'll tell you, when it gets
that way, everybody avoids him.
The (Asian) girls avoid him.
The guys avoid him.
The (dating) tour avoids him.
Nobody wants to be around a negative Nancy.
No.
So the reality is, it didn't
go your way, okay, that's life.
Sometimes it's not going to go your way.
So you put a smile on your face, and
you go make something else happen.
I think what happens sometimes is
guys, they get a little discouraged.
Maybe it didn't work well, and
they just want someone to blame.
So they're going to blame the hotel.
They're going to blame us.
They're going to blame somebody.
Whereas if they just
kept positive and kept
going, it would have
turned out well for them.
Alright, Max says, I don't know
how I feel about dating in a group.
I'd rather just video chat a girl
or two and then go meet them.
I mean, I'll say something
real quick and then you can
chime in, but I look, Max,
you can do whatever you like.
And certainly you can do that.
We have a lot of men that go over.
We call independently
and we will help set that up.
And we will arrange the meetings
when you get there. And that's wonderful.
But it's a long ways to go.
And even if you do a video call
with a (Asian) woman, you still, all
the senses are not in play yet.
It's not the same as meeting in
person. And to go all that way just
to meet one or two (Bangkok) women, if it
doesn't work, then you're coming back.
We have a gentleman right now
who I believe is in Eastern Europe,
went all the way to meet one
woman, didn't really work out very well.
He's coming back. That is a long
ways to go. Now we have also a (dating) tour
going there this week where they're
going to meet between the two socials.
It'll probably be about
250 to 300 (Asian) women that
they're going to get
the opportunity to meet.
You can still meet those
couple of women that you
want to video chat with.
You can make them priorities.
But why wouldn't you give
yourself every opportunity? I'm not
saying this to try to sell you
on something. I really don't care.
If you want to do the
group tour, that's wonderful.
If you want to go
individually, that's great too.
I'm just trying to give
you the benefit of my
experience over the last
30 years. And more is better.
More possibility is better.
When you have a limited amount
of time and you have to go
a long ways to accomplish it,
why wouldn't you give
yourself every opportunity?
And that's what I said. We kind
of talked about that a little earlier.
I think you ought to go
to the first two (speed dating) socials.
It's focused more on not who you're
interested in, but who's interested in you.
You're going to get 10
different tables. You're going to
pick one and try and find
one or two (Thai) girls at each table.
At the end of the day, you want
to have three or four or five girls
that you would be interested in
dating, should have pursued that way.
And then at the end of the
two socials, you have, what,
five to 10 girls that are
really interested in you.
And if you want to go do the
one where you just video chat
and do it, you may end up
finding yourself in that position.
If it doesn't work out. I did.
Yeah. I mean, you just don't know.
Two (Thai) girls I had that I was
settled on and I should have met
more and paid more attention
to who was interested in me.
But they ended up with
at the same time.
And I had a week to two weeks in there
where I'm twiddling my thumbs thinking,
you know, every night at Hillary 11,
watching the band sing is kind of fun.
But it's not as fun as being on a
date with someone you're in love with.